<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:paddingBottom="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    android:paddingLeft="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingRight="@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin"
    android:paddingTop="@dimen/activity_vertical_margin"
    app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior"
    tools:context="com.example.natalie.healthcareapp.LifestyleConsiderations"
    tools:showIn="@layout/activity_lifestyle_considerations">

    <ScrollView
        android:id="@+id/ScrollView01"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="480dip"
        android:layout_alignParentEnd="true">

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:singleLine="false"
            android:text="Sexuality \n\n you may notice a change in your sexual needs or repsonse. \n 1. Talk about it - with your partner and with us! \n 2. Your periods might stop - early menopause (hot flashes, mood swings, vaginal dryness). \n Talk with your oncologist about future pregnancies and family planning. \n\n Pregnancy must be avoided and for several months after completion of treatment. use condoms while either partner is receiving anticancer treatment. \n\n Anticancer Treatment may include: \n 1. Decreased sperm count - consider sperm banking \n 2. Permature Menopause - hot flahses, mood swings, and vaginal dryness. \n If you have any questions containing these two things, do call Supportive Care. \n\n\n Alcohol \n\n Do not drink on the day of your treatment. Alcohol may make your side effects worse. Alcohol may also interact with the ways some medications work. Talk with your oncologist about alcohol and drinking during your treatment. \n\n\n Smoking \n\n It is recommended that you try not to smoke or use any tobacco products. We are in a smoke-free hospital and cancer centre. This means that smoking is not allowed anywhere on the grounds, including parking lots, garages, and vehicles. For support in staying smoke-free, talk to a member of your health care team  at Hamilton Health Sciences or contact Smoker's Helpline at 1-877-513-5333 or www.smokershelpline.ca. \n\n\n Safety at Home \n\n For 7 days after taking anticancer drugs, wear gloves and keep soiled items from touching you when you clean up. \n\n 1. Body fluids such as urine, vomit, bowel movements or diarrhea. \n 2. Linens or bedsheets soiled with body fluids. \n\n Soiled Linens: wash separately with hot water and detergent. \n\n Rinsing Bedpans and Basins: wear gloves and rinse carefully \n\n Toilets: double flush toilets while on anti-cancer treatment. \n\n\n Visitors \n\n Visitors must be feeling well - no fevers, coughs or flu symptoms. \n\n\n"
            android:textSize="14dp"
            android:textStyle="normal"
            android:enabled="true"
            android:focusable="false"
            android:focusableInTouchMode="false"
            android:textAlignment="viewStart"
            android:visibility="visible" />
        textView.bringToFront();
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>
